socialmediamanagerschool.com 2019-07-09

# Privacy Policy - Social Media Manager School

**Our Commitment to Privacy** : 

Your privacy is important to us. We respect the privacy of every individual who visits this website. 

By using this website and/or joining Social Media Manager School, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, so please review the terms below. This privacy policy was last changed on May 23, 2018 to update for GDPR Requirements. 

**What information do we gather from you?**

We collect your name and email when you sign up for any of our free or paid offerings including ebooks, webinars, case studies, guides and other online documents. 

We collect your name, email, address, and phone number when you purchase a membership to the Social Media Manager School or Social Media Strategy School. 

We collect non-identifiable personal information using “cookies.” A cookie is a small data file that a website can transfer to your hard drive through your browser. The cookie is then stored on your computer as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer, but not you. You can set your browser to notify you if cookies are received, or set up your browser to not accept cookies. If you set your browser to block cookies, it may interfere with your ability to use our website to schedule appointments.   
  
We may collect some other personally identifying information about your use of our website in a non-identifiable format and combine it with other non-identifiable information, to be analyzed only at an aggregate level for marketing purposes.

**How do we use your information?**

We use your name and email to send you the specific information and/or program you have requested. We may use your name and email to send you marketing information and news. 

We use first-party and third-party cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so we can optimize our website and create a better user experience for you. We may use cookies via Google Analytics Advertising Features, Facebook Advertising, Twitter Advertising, LinkedIn Advertising, Pinterest Advertising, and YouTube Advertising for remarketing, impression reporting, and interest reporting. Click here to[ opt-out of Google Analytics cookies](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). If you want to block cookies completely, you can disable them in your browser:[ Chrome](http://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?hl=en),[ Firefox](http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences),[ Safari](http://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265), or[ Internet Explorer](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies). As stated above, if you set your browser to block cookies, it may interfere with your ability to use our shopping cart, make purchases, or use the membership system section of the website.

We do not respond to DNT (“Do Not Track”) privacy settings in your website browser. We may use third-party tracking services to provide data to optimize the services available on this website.   

**How do you unsubscribe, correct, update, review, or delete your information?**

You can unsubscribe to any email by clicking on a link at the bottom of the email. If you unsubscribe to emails when you are a member of Social Media Manager School, it will make it difficult for you to receive the benefits of your purchase. 

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by emailing support@socialmediamanagerschool.com. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. Our data retention policy is that you have control over us deleting your data; in other words, we will keep your data until you tell us to delete it. 

**How do we protect your information?**

All information gathered on behalf of Social Media Manager School is kept strictly confidential and is not sold or rented to any other company without notice to you. Information provided will be used solely to determine and send appropriate information about services or products. Social Media Manager School is located in the United States and any data you submit will be transferred to the United States. When you purchase from Social Media Manager School with credit card via the web, we protect and secure this information by employing commercially customary web-based security and encryption protocols, examples of which include Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and Secure Electronic Transaction (SET).To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our home page and on every page where personally identifiable information is requested.

We may use the following third parties to help us provide services to you: [ActiveCampaign](https://www.activecampaign.com/), [Zoom](https://zoom.us/), [Infusionsoft](https://www.infusionsoft.com/legal/privacy-policy), [LeadPages](https://www.leadpages.net/privacy), [Wishlist](http://wishlistmemberplugins.net/privacy-policy), [Demio](https://demio.com/privacy-policy), [Zapier, ](https://zapier.com/privacy/)and [GoToWebinar](https://www.logmeininc.com/legal/privacy). These third parties we may use to host your data will keep your data confidential according to their own Privacy Policies.

Circumstances may arise where we may decide to sell, buy, merge, or otherwise reorganize our business in the United States or elsewhere, or where we may decide to share, rent, buy, or sell business assets for reorganizing, developing, or expanding our business. It is our policy to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions. If the company assets or our entire company is acquired, then the lists of personally identifiable information and other contact information will likely be one of the assets acquired.   

**Information Regarding Children**  
  
This website is not directed to people who are under 13 years of age. We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Please notify us at support@socialmediamanagerschool.com if you are a parent whose child has provided us with personally identifying information, and we will delete such information from our files.   
  
**California Residents Privacy Rights**  
  
If you are a California resident, under “Shine the Light law” (Cal Civ Code Section 1798.83) you can request the disclosure of certain personal information that we have disclosed to third parties for marketing purposes in the last year. To make a request, contact us at [support@socialmediamanagerschool.com](mailto:support@socialmediamanagerschool.com).

**Questions Regarding This Policy**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, please direct them to: [support@socialmediamanagerschool.com](mailto:support@socialmediamanagerschool.com) If you are a European Union resident and you are dissatisfied with how we have managed a complaint, you are entitled to contact your local data protection authority.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.
